词组和断句。用标点来处理断句。逗号听起来不同于
Word groups and phrasing. Use punctuation for phrasing. Commas sound different from
句号。停顿可以服务于相关想法、观点，或只是换气。到目前为止，你已经
periods. Pauses for related thoughts, ideas, or for breathing. By now, you've
开始形成强语调，有清晰的峰和弱化的谷，
begun developing a strong intonation with clear peaks and reduced valleys, so you're
准备好进入下一步了。你可能会发现自己像这样朗读这段。
ready for the next step. You may find yourself reading the paragraph like this.
Hello, my name is so-and-so. I'm taking American accent training. If so, your
听众不会完全理解或享受你的演讲。
audience won't completely comprehend or enjoy your presentation. In addition to
除了语调，还有另一种表达意义的语音层面。
intonation, there's another aspect of speech that indicates meaning. This can be
你有没有只听到一小段谈话，
called phrasing or tone. Have you ever caught just a snippet of a conversation in
自己的语言，只听到片段，却能以某种方式拼出前后内容吗？
your own language and somehow known how to piece together what came before or after
这和意群有关。在句子中，断句会告诉你
the part you heard? This has to do with phrasing. In a sentence, phrasing tells
听者会知道说话人此刻说到哪里、接下来要往哪里去，以及
the listener where the speaker is at the moment, where the speaker is going, and if
请注意，语调仍然落在名词上。
the speaker is finished or not. Note that the intonation stays on the nouns.